import React from 'react';

export const kabhubData = [
  {
    key: 1,
    data:
    { question: 'Some place holder question?',
      answer: "Your safety is our number one priority, please do get in touch if you have any concern about safety anytime during your trip or experience. If there is threat to your health or security, please do contact emergency services or the police immediately. lfyou have been threatened or harassed by anyone connected to Huptown during your trip, please report the situation to us or directly to the police"
    }
  },
  {
    key: 2,
    data:
    { question: 'Can a Minor Travel Alone?',
      answer: "The minimum age to open an account on Huptown is 18. Children under the age of 14 travelling on an adult's account must be accompanied.With signed permission from parents or guardians with ID shown to the driver, minors between 11 and 14 may be allowed to travel alone."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 3,
    data:
    { question: 'Have an Issue with a Trip?',
      answer: "If you forgot something orhave an issue with a trip that has been completed, go to ILjp History and use the feedback form in your app. We are always happy to help. If the issue is about an ongoing trip, you can contact support by sending a message or giving us a call directly through your app. (standard I-JK call rates apply]. As phone lines may be busy, we encourage you to send a message.Our team will deal with your concern as soon as possible."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 4,
    data:
    { question: 'There is Issue With My App.What Should I do?',
      answer: "Sometimes you may encounter a frozen screen or have trouble navigating between pages, this may be due to poor internet connection. You should check that your connection is fine. If the fault is not your internet, you should try to close the app and open it again. If you still encounter the same problem, try again after some time and if the problem persists, you should consider deleting your app and reinstalling again, or contact our support team for assistance. 5. How Does Advance Bookings Work? All pre-booked trips can be found under My Bookings. You can request a car anytime on demand or up to 30 days in advance. To amend a booking, click the edit button and save your new details."
}
  },
  {
    key: 5,
    data:
    { question: 'How Does Advance Bookings Work?',
      answer: "All pre-booked trips can be found under My Bookings. You can request a car anytime on demand or up to 30 days in advance. To amend a booking, click the edit button and save your new details."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 6,
    data:
    { question: 'When Is Payment Taken?',
      answer: "We charge your card at the end of every journey, however, at the time of booking, our secure payment system will contact your bank for pre-authorization to check the validity of your card and check if you have sufficient amount for the trip."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 7,
    data:
    { question: 'Will I Get Charged For Cancelling a Trip?',
      answer: "A cancellation fee of £5 will apply if your driver has arrived at your destination before cancellation occurs. We will charge up to £0.50 for every 5 minutes wait after your driver has arrived at your place. "
    }
  },
  {
    key: 8,
    data:
    { question: 'How Does Tipping Work?',
      answer: "We hope that you have a pleasant trip. if you're impressed, we encourage you to leave a small tip for your driver at the completion of your trip within the app."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 9,
    data:
    { question: 'How Can I Request a Ride from The Airport?',
      answer: "To request a ride from the airport, you should come out of your arrival terminal\n\n(a) Heathrow Airport Requests\nTerminal 2 - Level 1: wait for the driver Short Stay area on Row L.\nTerminal 3 - Level 3: wait for the driver Short Stay area on Row A.\nTerminal 4 - Level 1: wait for the driver at the Short Stay area near the Central Lifts.\nTerminal 5 - Level 1 wait for the driver Short Stay area on Row A & F.\n\n(b) Gatwick Requests\nAt South Terminal — Go to Orange Car Park: wait for your driver at Level 3 on Row A\nAt North Terminal - Go to Car Park 5: wait for driver at Level 3 Row B.\n\n(c) London City Airport Requests. \nYou can find your driver at the Short stay car park\n\n(d) London Stansted Requests \nYou can find your Huptown driver outside the main terminal."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 10,
    data:
    { question: 'Accessibility',
      answer: "If you or any of your loved ones have special requirements such as wheelchair access, please bear with us as we are currently working to improve access and user experience for everyone."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 11,
    data:
    { question: 'How can I send a Feedback?',
      answer: "For feedback and suggestions. Please use the support section in your app to leave a feedback for us."
    }
  },
]





export const experienceData = [
  {
    key: 1,
    data:
    { question: 'What is XPerience?',
      answer: "Xperience is our end to end feature that allows anyone to book their favourite attractions,gigs, festivals, restaurants and so on. Xperience combines mobility with innovative ticketing technology, which means that it enables you to discover, book, and visit magical destinations locally and all around the World."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 2,
    data:
    { question: 'What is Fan-X and how can I use it?',
      answer: "Fan-X is our ticket resale category where you can resell your Xperience ticket or voucher in case you can't make it.lf you want to cancel your existing experience and resell it on Huptown, please get in touch via supportuk@huptown.com. Our ticket resell site will be up soon. Note that you can also sell tickets or vouchers to events not initially bought from Huptown."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 3,
    data:
    { question: 'There Was an Issue with My XPerience Trip.',
      answer: "(a) If you have an issue with an Xperience trip that has been completed, go to Trip History and use the feedback form in your app. We are always happy to help.\n\n(b) If your concern is about an ongoing trip, you can contact Support by sending a message. You can also give us a call directly through your app. (standard IJK call rates apply). As phone lines may be busy, we encourage you to send a message. Our team will deal with your concern as asa. soon as possible.\n\n(c) If it is regarding a booking, you can contact us through support from your app menu.\n\n(d) If your QR code cannot be scanned, you should contact us directly through support using the call feature or better still send us a message. We promise to respond immediately. \n\n(e) If there is an error in your booking, you should contact us directly through the support feature in your app or better still send us a message. We promise to respond immediately."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 4,
    data:
    { question: 'How Are Charges Calculated?',
      answer: "All charges are calculated based on the Xperience fee shown plus your trip to the Xperience destination. Fee for your return trip are also added if you book a return trip with Huptown."
}
  },
  {
    key: 5,
    data:
    { question: 'Can I Amend The Location?',
      answer: "If your experience is offered in more than one location, you can amend to another location. You should do this by editing your booking at least 5 hours before your scheduled time. Do bear in mind that there may be cost differences between different addresses, which will reflect in your new quote when an amendment is done. We are unable to refund the cost difference because of the time and stress in processing refunds if less than £1O"
    }
  },
  {
    key: 6,
    data:
    { question: 'When Should I Book an XPerience?',
      answer: "Experiences can be booked at any time in advance, however, it is always best to schedule one few weeks ordays before your preferred date, as spaces may be limited."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 7,
    data:
    { question: 'Can I Cancel My XPerience Booking?',
      answer: "If you're unable to attend your experience booking for whatsoever reason, you should amend to a more convenient date or time as early as possible and at least 5 hours before your scheduled time. For time bound events where no other time or date is available, you will be unable to amend. However, if you have a strong reason to cancel, you should do so three days before the scheduled time of your experience booking.You will soon be able to list your unused voucheror ticket on Fan-x on Huptown forresale."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 8,
    data:
    { question: 'When will my Driver Arrive?',
      answer: " We account for the time duration of your trip to your experience destination, hence, your experience manager (driver) will arrive minutes before the actual experience time, depending on your location."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 9,
    data:
    { question: 'When is Payment Taken For My Booking?',
      answer: "Payments are taken for the total quotes shown upon the completion of your booking. You should ensure that a booking is only completed once payment is available in your bank account. Charges include your experience fee and the total fare of your return trip to your destination and back, if a return is booked."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 10,
    data:
    { question: 'Do I Have to Tip my Experience Manager [Driver)?',
      answer: "You don't have to give a tip, however, if you're impressed with quality of your in-car experience, we encourage you to show a kind gesture by leaving a tip completely at your own discretion."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 11,
    data:
    { question: 'How Can I Gain Entry at The Venue or Location?',
      answer: "If you have paid for your experience at the time of booking, you should show your QR code, which was generated at the point of booking at the venue for admission. You can find your QR code in your app menu, under My Booking.You may need paper ticket in some cases to gain entry to some experiences, which will be emailed or mailed to you. Our team will be in touch in such case."
    }
  },
  {
    key: 12,
    data:
    { question: 'What is Huptown XP?',
      answer: "In case you come across the term, Huptown XP, this refers to one of the businesses providing unique experiences on our platform. Huptown XP means that you can find the company or event on the Huptown app. It is different from XPerience, which is the Huptown platform where you discover magical experiences in your app."
    }
  },
]
